MINAHIL NAWAZ

CERTIFIED SFCC FRONT END DEVELOPER

CONTACT

0307 0562260

minahil1323@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/minahil-nawaz-0343691b9

minahilnawaz.github.io

SKILLS

HTML5 jQuery, Javascript

CSS3 ReactNative

SCSS Sfcc

Bootstrap Photoshop

EDUCATION

BS Software Engineering

Punjab University College of Information technology

2016-2020 3.36/4.0

FYP: A Computer Vision based system to determine crop health

INTERESTS

Gaming

Travelling

Music

Seasons

LANGUAGES

English

Urdu

German

ABOUT

Over 3 Years of working experience having good command over Front-End Development.

Having proficient knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SCSS, ReactJS, jQuery, Ionic and many of the CSS frameworks like Bootstrap, Foundation, Semantic UI and google Materialize

Transforming complex layout PSDs into pixel-perfect presentation-layer HTML5/CSS3 templates

Produced multiple visual elements of web application by translating UI/UX design.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sfcc Front end developer

Systems Limited August, 2020 - Present

- Worked as Sfcc front-end developer
- Exposure of making components in page designer and experience of working in an agile team and transforming figma into pixel-perfect presentation-layer HTML5/CSS3 templates.

React Native Intern

ShopDev March, 2020 - June, 2020

- · Worked as React Native intern.
- Used understanding of React fundamentals to promote better component lifecycle practices and worked on various screens of the Aimfit application.

PROJECTS

kadewe.de

- Worked on its SFRA implementation on different pages and also created various page designer components.
- Design its loyalty program from scratch.
- Worked on improving site performance by removing redundant code and unused CSS.
- Converted new designs using the following skills · HTML 5 · CSS 3 · SCSS · JQuery · Bootstrap · Webpack.
- Design static pages through page designer and added animations.

Khaadi Sfra

- Worked on its sfra implementation. Design website from scratch.
- Design homepage, header , footer , checkout , myaccount etc.
- Design static pages through page designer and added animations.

Sapphire Sfra

- Worked on its sfra implementation. Design website from scratch including header, footer, plp,pdp and homepage etc.
- Design static pages through page designer and added animations.

CERTIFICATIONS

B2C Salesforce Commerce Developer